Finding Aid for the CBS Inc. Film and Television Collection PASC-M.0072
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Programs, Series 4.
  - The Line Up -- Recording Logs, Subseries 82.
    - Samson Magill, February 25, 1958 (Box 1161, Folder 7)
      On item, "Samson Magill / Prod. #134 / Music Log sent: 25 Feb. '58."
    - Dr. George Jeremy, February 18, 1958 (Box 1161, Folder 8)
      On item, "Dr. George Jeremy / Prod. #142 / Music Log sent: 18 Feb. '58."
    - The G.I. Shoe, February 13, 1958 (Box 1161, Folder 9)
      On item, "The G. I. Shoe / Prod. #136 / Music Log sent: 13 Feb. '58."
    - Deacon Whitehall, February 12, 1958 (Box 1161, Folder 10)
      On item, "Deacon Whitehall / Prod. #145 / Music Log sent: 12 Feb. '58."
    - High Fashion, February 4, 1958 (Box 1161, Folder 11)
      On container, "High Fashion / Prod. #138 / Music Log sent: 4 Feb. '58."
    - The Harger Jamison Case, July 11, 1957 (Box 1161, Folder 12)
      On item, "The Harger Jamison Case / Prod. #123 / Cue sheet sent: 11 July '57."
    - The 17643 Case, Juny 2, 1957 (Box 1161, Folder 13)
      On item, "The 17643 Case / Prod. #117 / Cue sheets sent: 2 July '57."
    - The Rufus Granger Case, September 25, 1958 (Box 1162, Folder 1)
      On item, "Rufus Granger Case / Prod. #166-171 / Music Log sent: 25 Sept. '58."
    - The Phantom Robber, October 30, 1957 (Box 1162, Folder 2)
      On item, "The Phantom Robber / Prod. #129 / Cue sheet sent: 30 Oct. '57."
    - The Scottie Waterford Case, October 30, 1957 (Box 1162, Folder 3)
      On item, "Scottie Waterford Case / Prod. #169-174 / Music Log sent: 30 Oct. '58."
    - The Girl Bandit Case, October 29, 1958 (Box 1162, Folder 4)
      On item, "Girl Bandit Case / Prod. #163-161 / Music Log sent: 29 Oct. '58."
    - The Chloroform Murder Case, November 12, 1958 (Box 1162, Folder 5)
      On item, "Chloroform Murder Case / Prod. #178-182 / Music Log sent: 12 Nov. '58."
    - The Chick Madison Case, October 29, 1958 (Box 1162, Folder 6)
      On item, "Chick Madison Case / Prod. #167-172 / Music Log sent: 29 Oct. '58."
    - The Little Hero Case, July 11, 1957 (Box 1162, Folder 7)
      On item, "The Little Hero Case / Prod. #119 / Cue sheet sent: 11 July '57."
    - The Boylston Billing Case, November 25, 1958 (Box 1162, Folder 8)
      On item, "Boylston Billing Case / Prod. #182-184 / Music Log sent: 25 Nov. '58."
    - The Veiled Lady Case, November 6, 1958 (Box 1162, Folder 9)
      On item, "Veiled Lady Case / Prod. #152-163 / Music Log sent: 6 Nov. '58."
    - The Scott Franklin Case, January 8, 1958 (Box 1162, Folder 11)
      On item, "Scott Franklin Case / Prod. #143 / Cue sheet sent: 8 Jan. '58."
    - The Pawn Ticket Case, December 24, 1957 (Box 1162, Folder 12)
      On item, "Pawn Ticket Case / Prod. #141 / Cue sheet sent: 24 Dec. '57."
    - The Sam Bradford Case, December 10, 1957 (Box 1162, Folder 13)
      On item, "Sam Bradford Case / Prod. #144 / Cue sheet sent: 10 Dec. '57."
    - The Franklin Case, November 10, 1955 (Box 1163, Folder 1)
      On item, "Franklin Case / Prod. No. 47-47 / Cue sheet sent: 11-10-55."
    - The Jealous Mambo Dancer, January 28, 1958 (Box 1163, Folder 2)
      On item, "The Jealous Mambo Dancer / Prod. #135 / Music Log sent: 28 Jan. '58."
    - The Firebug Case, December 4, 1957 (Box 1163, Folder 3)
      On item, "The Firebug Case / Prod. #127 / Cue sheet sent: 4 Dec. '57."
    - The Winner Take Nothing Case, October 2, 1958 (Box 1163, Folder 4)
      On item, "Winner Take Nothing Case / Prod. #175-178 / Music Log sent: 2 Oct. '58."
    - Slowboat Murphy, January 29, 1958 (Box 1163, Folder 5)
      On item, "Slowboat Murphy / Prod. #131 / Music Log sent: 29 Jan. '58."
    - The Clarence Culver Case, January 15, 1958 (Box 1163, Folder 6)
      On item, "Clarence Culver Case / Prod. #126 / Music Log sent: 15 Jan. '58."
    - The Phoney Witness Case, August 8, 1957 (Box 1163, Folder 7)
      On item, "Phoney Witness Case / Prod. #125 / Cue sheets sent: 8 Aug. '57 / Licence pending: Rec'd.: 27 Aug '57 / Impress: $10.00 (4)."
    - The Security Officer, August 6, 1957 (Box 1163, Folder 8)
      On item, "Security Officer / Prod. #122 / Cue sheets sent: 6 Aug. '57."
    - The Hot Shot Robbery, November 27, 1957 (Box 1163, Folder 9)
      On item, "Hot Shot Robbery / Prod. #137 / Cue sheet sent: 27 Nov. '57."
    - Donald Damen, November 18, 1957 (Box 1163, Folder 10)
      On item, "Donald Damen / Prod. #140 / Cue sheet sent: 18 Nov. '57."
    - The Ash Blonde Model, November 12, 1957 (Box 1163, Folder 11)
      On item, "Ash Blonde Model / Prod. #128 / Cue sheet sent: 12 Nov. '57."
    - The Hamilton Harker Case, December 29, 1958 (Box 1163, Folder 12)
      On item, "Hamilton Harker Case / Prod. #183-185 / Music Log sent: 29 Dec. '58."
    - The Happy Janitor Case, July 2, 1957 (Box 1164, Folder 1)
      On item, "The Happy Janitor Case / Prod. #118 / Cue sheets sent: 2 July '57 / Licence pending: Ascher (Inter-Art) $5.00."
    - The Missing Crime, July 5, 1957 (Box 1164, Folder 2)
      On item, "The Missing Crime / Prod. #116 / Cue sheets sent: 5 June '57."
    - The Goode Case, April 5, 1957 (Box 1164, Folder 3)
      On item, "The Goode Case / Prod. #109 / Cue sheets sent: 5 April '57."
    - The Stanely Devlin Case, March 26, 1957 (Box 1164, Folder 4)
      On item, "Stanley Devlin Case / Prod. #112 / Cue sheets sent: 26 March '57."
    - The Unwelcome Visitor, March 22, 1957 (Box 1164, Folder 5)
      On item, "Unwelcome Visitor / Prod. #113 / Cue sheets sent: 22 March '57."
    - My Son is a Stranger, October 6, 1959 (Box 1164, Folder 6)
      On item, "My Son Is A Stranger / Prod. #174-208 / Music Log sent: 6 Oct. '59."
    - Death of a Puppet, October 14, 1959 (Box 1164, Folder 7)
      On item, "Death Of A Puppet / Prod. #174-209 / Music Log sent: 14 Oct. '59 / Licence Pending: Inter Art Co. Ltd. - $5.00 / Inter Art (Impress) - $15.00 / Rec'd. 23 Nov. '59."
    - The Edge of Disaster, October 23, 1959 (Box 1164, Folder 8)
      On item, "Edge Of Disaster (formerly Jiggling Jimmy) / Prod. #174-210 / Music Log sent: 23 Oct. '59."
    - Robert Ericson, January 9, 1957 (Box 1164, Folder 9)
      On item, "Robert Ericson / Prod. #104 / Cue Sheets sent: 1-9-57 / Receiv'd: 1-21-57."
    - The Corny Cassidy Case, December 17, 1958 (Box 1164, Folder 10)
      On item, "Corny Cassidy Case / Prod. #154-167 / Music Log sent: 17 Dec. '58."
    - The Juke Box Bandit, January 3, 1957 (Box 1165, Folder 1)
      On item, "Juke Box Bandit / Prod. #97 / Cue sheets sent: 1-3-57 / Licence pending: Inter Art 5.00 / Impress 10.00."
    - Heinrich Menzel, February 14, 1957 (Box 1165, Folder 2)
      On item, "Heinrich Menzel / Prod. #96 / Cue sheets sent: 14 Feb. '57."
    - The Sailor's Wife, February 12, 1957 (Box 1165, Folder 3)
      On item, "Sailor's Wife / Prod. #106 / Cue sheets sent: 12 Feb. '57."
    - The Cherokee Rose Case, January 31, 1957 (Box 1165, Folder 4)
      On item, "Cherokee Rose Case / Prod. #111 / Cue sheets sent: 1-31-57."
    - Walking Deadman, January 23, 1957 (Box 1165, Folder 5)
      On item, "Walking Deadman / Prod. #91 / Cue sheets sent: 1-23-57."
    - The Charlene Bleak Case, January 23, 1957 (Box 1165, Folder 6)
      On item, "Charlene Bleak Case / Prod. #105 / Cue sheets sent: 1-23-57."
    - Seven Sinners, January 15, 1960 (Box 1165, Folder 7)
      On item, "Seven Sinners / Prod. #174-218 / Music Log sent: 15 Jan. '60 / Licence Pending: - Inter Art Co. Ltd. - $5.00."
    - Run to the City, November 3, 1959 (Box 1165, Folder 8)
      On item, "Run To The City / Prod. #174-211 / Music Log sent: 3 Nov. '59 / Licence Pending: Mutel $15.00 - Rec'd 20 Nov. '59 / Inter Art Co. Ltd. $15.00 - Rec'd 20 Nov. '59."
    - The Girls and Guns Case, November 3, 1959 (Box 1165, Folder 9)
      On item, "Girls And Guns Case / Prod. #168-173 / Music Log sent: 28 Jan. '59."
    - The Daniel Leadley Case, February 6, 1959 (Box 1165, Folder 10)
      On item, "Daniel Leadley Case / Prod. #176-180 / Music Log sent: 6 Feb. '59 / Licence Pending - Inter Art Co. Ltd.: $5.00."
    - The Charlie Cleveland Case, January 5, 1959 (Box 1166, Folder 1)
      On item, "Charlie Cleveland Case / Prod. #177-181 / Music Log sent: 5 Jan. '59 / Licence Pending: Inter Art Co. Ltd. - $10.00 - Rec'd - 2 Mar. '59."
    - Wake Up to Terror, August 31, 1959 (Box 1166, Folder 2)
      On item, "Wake Up To Terror / The Irwin Mapes Case / Prod. #174-206 / Music Log sent: 31 Aug. '59 / Revised: 1 Oct. '59."
    - The Big Score Case, August 22, 1958 (Box 1166, Folder 4)
      On item, "The Big Score Case / Prod. #153 / Music Log sent: 22 Aug. '58."
    - The Strange Return of Army Armitage, September 23, 1959 (Box 1166, Folder 5)
      On item, "The Strange Return Of Army Armitage / prod. #174-207 / Music Log sent: 23 Sept. '59."
    - The China Town Case, October 28, 1955 (Box 1171, Folder 2)
      On item, "China-town case / Prod. #42-49 / Cue sheet sent: (Music clearance enclosed) / Music Licenses Received (check mark)."
    - The Drugstore Cowgirl Case, February 6, 1959 (Box 1171, Folder 11)
      On item, "Drugstore Cowgirl Case / Prod. #158-158 / Music Log sent: 6 Feb. '59."
    - The Waterfront Romeo Case, January 19, 1959 (Box 1171, Folder 12)
      On item, "Waterfront Romeo Case / Prod. #156-155 / Music Log sent: 19 Jan. '59."
    - The Pidgeon Drop Case, January 26, 1959 (Box 1173, Folder 1)
      On item, "Pigeon Drop Case / Prod. #164-164 / Music Log sent: 26 Jan. '59."
    - The Dennis Case, November 1, 1955 (Box 1173, Folder 2)
      On container, "The Dennis Case / Prod. #50-54 / 12-2-55."
    - The Murdered Blonde Case, March 2, 1959 (Box 1173, Folder 8)
      On item, "Murdered Blonde Case / Prod. #180-170 / Music Log sent: 2 Mar. '59."
    - The Changeable Blonde Case, March 2, 1959 (Box 1173, Folder 9)
      On item, "Changeable Blonde Case / Prod. #165-165 / Music Log sent: 2 Mar. '59."
    - The D.V.B. Cuddington Case, February 20, 1959 (Box 1173, Folder 10)
      On item, "D.V.B. Cuddington Case / Prod. #161-169 / Music Log sent: 20 Feb. '59."
    - The Big Dan McGran Case, January 7, 1959 (Box 1176, Folder 5)
      On item, "Big Dan McGran Case / Prod. #179-154 / Music Log sent: 7 Jan. '59."
    - The Trapdoor Spider Case, January 26, 1959 (Box 1176, Folder 6)
      On item, "Trapdoor Spider Case / Prod. #150-149 / Music Log sent: 26 Jan. '59."
    - The Ambitious Peddler, March 14, 1957 (Box 1176, Folder 7)
      On item, "Ambitious Peddler / Prod. #107 / Cue sheets sent: 14 Mar. '57."
    - The Robert Avery Case, February 25, 1957 (Box 1177, Folder 1)
      On item, "Robert Avery Case / Prod. #102 / Cue sheets sent: 25 Feb. '57."
    - The Prince of Penmen, December 28, 1959 (Box 1177, Folder 2)
      On item, "Prince of Penmen / Prod. #174-215 / Music Log sent: 28 Dec. '59."
    - The counterfeit Citizen, November 24, 1959 (Box 1177, Folder 3)
      On item, "Counterfeit Citizen / Prod. #174-214 / Music Log sent: 24 Nov. '59 / Licence Pending: - Capitol - $15.00."
    - Lonesome as Midnight, November 16, 1959 (Box 1177, Folder 4)
      On item, "Lonesome As Midnight / Prod. #174-213 / Music Log sent: 16 Nov. '59."
    - The Chinatown Story, December 4, 1959 (Box 1177, Folder 5)
      On item, "Chinatown Story / Prod. #174-212 / Music Log sent: 4 Dec. '59 / Licence Pending: Inter Art Co. Ltd. $5.00 / Mee Shing Radio Co. $25.00 / Capitol $20.00 / Mutel $15.00."
    - The Transom Burglar, March 4, 1957 (Box 1177, Folder 7)
      On item, "Transom Burglar / Prod. #95 / Cue sheets sent: 4 Mar. '57."
    - The Georgie Gillette Case, February 26, 1957 (Box 1177, Folder 8)
      On item, "Georgie Gillette Case / Prod. #98 / Cue sheets sent: 26 Feb. '57."
  - The Line Up -- Scores, Subseries 157.
    - Theme, manuscript score; ozalid (Box 95)
      Score no.: CPN5810.
  - The Line Up -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 83.
    - [Contents Unidentified], May 14, 1959; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1142, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS Line Up/Pre-Score/Piano + Vocal/5-14-49/"King Con Case"/"Imagination"."
    - The Garmen Millingham Case, November 5, 1958 (Box 1162, Folder 10)
      On item, "The Garmen Millingham Case / Prod. #173-177 / Music Log sent: '58."
  - Lost in Space -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 84.
    - End Title, 1/4 in. tape (Box 1145, Folder 6)
      On container, "Gene Feldman/M.22 + End Title."
  - Lou Grant -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 85.
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 19, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 1)
      On container, "Prod 1501/R13/9-19-82."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 19, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 2)
      On container, "Prod 1501/R15/9-19-82."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 18, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 3)
      On container, "Prod 1501/R11/9-18-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 18, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 4)
      On container, "Prod 1501/R12/9-18-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 19, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 5)
      On container, "Prod 1501/R14/9-19-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 18, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 6)
      On container, "Prod 1501/R10/9-18-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 17, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 7)
      On contianer, "Prod 1501/R8/9-17-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 17, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 8)
      On container, "Prod 1501/R9/9-17-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 17, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 9)
      On container, "Prod 1501/R100X/10-7-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 24, 1982; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 10)
      On container, "Prod 1502/R4/9-24-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 24, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 11)
      On container, "Prod 1502/R5/9-24-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 25, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 12)
      On container, "Prod 1502/R6/9-25-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 24, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 13)
      On container, "Prod 1502/R7/9-25-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 25, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 14)
      On container, "Prod 1502/R8/9-25-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 28, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 15)
      On container, "Prod 1502/R11/9-28-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 29, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 16)
      On container, "Prod 1502/R14/9-29-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 12, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 17)
      On container, "Prod 1503/R17/10-12-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 14, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 18)
      On container, "Prod 1504/R4/10-14-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 16, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 19)
      On container, "Prod 1504/R9/10-16-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 17, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 20)
      On container, "Prod 1504/R10/10-17-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 17, 1981; open reel tape (Box 1055, Folder 21)
      On container, "Prod 1504/RX1/10-17-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 13, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 1)
      On container, "Prod 1504 R1 10-13-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 13, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 2)
      On container, "Prod 1504 R2 10-13-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 15, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 3)
      On container, "Prod 1504 R5 10-15-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 9, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 4)
      On container, "Prod 1503 R13 10-9-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 12, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 5)
      On container, "Prod 1503 R14 10-12-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 12, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 6)
      On container, "Prod 1503 R15 10-12-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 12, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 7)
      On container, "Prod 1503 R16 10-12-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 8, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 8)
      On container, "Prod 1503 R10 10-8-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 28, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 9)
      On container, "Prod 1502 R9 9-28-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 29, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 10)
      On container, "Prod 1502 R13 9-29-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 28, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 11)
      On container, "Prod 1502 R10 9-28-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 7, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 12)
      On container, "Prod 1503 R9 10-7-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 28, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 13)
      On container, "Prod 1502 R12 9-28-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 19, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1150, Folder 14)
      On container, "Prod 1504 R11 10-19-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 14, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1152, Folder 8)
      On container, "Prod 1504 R3 10-14-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 6, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1152, Folder 9)
      On container, "Prod 1503 R7 10-6-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], October 7, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1152, Folder 10)
      On container, "Prod 1503 R8 10-7-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 20, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1152, Folder 11)
      On container, "Prod 1501 R16 9-20-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 20, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1152, Folder 12)
      On container, "Prod 1501 R17 9-20-81."
    - [Contents Unidentified], September 20, 1981; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1152, Folder 13)
      On container, "Prod 1501 R18 9-20-81."
  - Magnum P.I. -- Papers, Subseries 86.
    - Press Information, 1986 July 30; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
      Describes the plot of two episodes to air in August and September.
    - Press Information, 1986 November 11; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
  - Man From the Riviera -- Scores, Subseries 161.
    - Gold and Gold (episode title), 1959 September 14; ozalid (Box 98)
      Score no: CPN5817
  - Manhattan Nights -- Scripts, Subseries 87.
    - A Midsummer Night's Reality, June 1, 1990; 81 p. (Box 1762)
      Revised throughout June 1-19, 1990. Production #0102. Production script. Script is incomplete (pages missing). Written by Tammy Ader. Directed by Sheldon Larry.
    - Hope and Glory, June 8, 1990; 59 p. (Box 1762)
      Production #0103. Written by Nick Harding. Directed by Steve Dubin.
    - Pilot, May 29, 1990; 61 p. (Box 1762)
      Production #0101. Written by Robin Green. Directed by Kim Friedman.
      On cover, "Final Draft."
    - Pilot, May 29, 1990; 49 p. (Box 1762)
  - Mannix--Sound Recordings, Subseries 145.
    - Unidentified Contents, 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3092)
  - Mary Tyler Moore Show--Sound Recordings, Subseries 142.
    - Unidentified Contents, 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3092)
  - MASH--Sound Recordings, Subseries 147.
    - Unidentified Contents, 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3092)
  - Medical Center--Sound Recordings, Subseries 144.
    - Unidentified Contents, 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3092)
  - The Millionaire -- Scores, Subseries 158.
    - Tom Hampton (episode title), 1959 November 2; ozalid (Box 96)
      Score no: CPN5832
    - Maggie Dalton (episode title), 1960 May 15; manuscript score, copy (Box 105)
      Score no: CPN5910.
    - Susan Johnson (episode title), copy (Box 106)
      Score no: CPN5895. Includes breakdown
  - Mike Hammer -- Papers, Subseries 88.
    - Cast and Production Credits, 1986 September 12; 2 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
    - Press Information, 1986 September 15; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
  - Mike Hammer -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 89.
    - Main Title, End Credits, 1986 May 7; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1154, Folder 7)
  - Mr. Adams and Eve -- Recording Logs, Subseries 90.
    - Production no. 8352, 07/22/1958 (Box 1166, Folder 6)
      On item, "Teenage Idol / Prod. #8351 / Music Log sent: 22 July '58."
    - Production no. 8331, 04/07/1958 (Box 1166, Folder 7)
      On item, "Adam & Eve & Ida / Prod. #8331 / Music Log sent: 7 Apr. '58."
    - Production no. 8333, 04/15/1958 (Box 1166, Folder 8)
      On item, "The Original MacDuffs / Prod. #8333 / Music Log sent: 15 Apr. '58."
    - Production no. 8329, 04/25/1958 (Box 1166, Folder 9)
      On item, "Ghosts Of Consolidated / Prod. #8329 / Music Log sent: 25 Apr. '58."
    - Production no. 8343, 05/29/1958 (Box 1175, Folder 9)
      On item, "The Chowder Cup / Prod. #8343 / Music Log sent: 29 May '58."
    - Production no. 8341, 05/19/1958 (Box 1175, Folder 10)
      On item, "The Interview / Prod. #8341 / Music Log sent: 19 May '58."
    - Production no. 8339, 05/09/1958 (Box 1175, Folder 11)
      On item, "Stunt Man / Prod. #8339 / Music Log sent: 9 May '58."
    - Production no. 8347, 06/13/1958 (Box 1176, Folder 3)
      On item, "Steve's Girl Friend / Prod. #8347 / Music Log sent: 13 June '58."
    - Production no. 8345, 06/09/1958 (Box 1176, Folder 4)
      On item, "Dear Variety / Prod. #8345 / Music Log sent: 9 June ' 58."
    - Production no. 8349, 07/09/1958 (Box 1176, Folder 8)
      On item, "Airplans In The Night / Prod. #8349 / Music Log sent: 9 July '58."
  - Mountain Man -- Scores, Subseries 166.
    - Unidentified Score, manuscript score (Box 103)
      Score no: CPN5903. Foreign Library: folders 2471-2480
    - Unidentified Score, manuscript score (Box 103)
    - Pilot Episode., 1960 April 11; manuscript score (Box 106)
      Full score, parts
      Score no: CPN5903.
  - Movie themes
    - Recording logs, 1978 (Box 1560)
  - Murder, She Wrote -- Papers, Subseries 91.
    Plot: Former substitute English teacher and famed mystery writer Jessica Fletcher has a gift for solving mysteries. You see, it seems murder follows her around, whether it be to the houses of her seemingly endless number of friends, nieces, and nephews or right in her hometown of Cabot Cove, Maine. Jessica is sometimes assisted by her friend Dr. Seth Hazelet or the local sheriff, Amos Tupper (later Sheriff Metsger). Sometimes, early in the series, Jessica would only narrate the episode, which would be a dramatization of one of her novels. In later seasons, Jessica moved to New York City to be closer to her publisher and also closer to crime.
    - Press Information, 1986 July 30; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
    - Press Information, 1986 September 15; 2 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
    - Press Information, 1986 November 11; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
    - Press Information, 1986 July 18; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
    - Press Information, 1986 July 30; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
  - My Sister Sam -- Papers, Subseries 92.
    - Cast and Production Credits, 1986 September 19; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 11)
  - Navy Log -- Recording Logs, Subseries 93.
    Half-hour anthology series about the military.
    - Episode 10: The Transfer, 11/10/1955 (Box 1166, Folder 3)
      On item, "The Transfer / Prod. #5512 / Cue sheets sent: 11-10-55."
    - Episode 18: Operation Typwriter, 01/03/1956 (Box 1167, Folder 1)
      On item, "The Typewriter / Prod. #5513 / Cue sheets sent: 1-3-56."
    - Episode 16: The Bomb, 12/12/1955 (Box 1168, Folder 5)
      On item, "The Bomb / Prod. #5525 / Music cue sheets sent: 12-12-55."
    - Episode 22: Lunger at Kunsan, 01/19/1956 (Box 1168, Folder 6)
      On item, "Lunger Of Kunsan / Prod. #5524 / Cue sheets sent: 1-19-56."
    - Episode 17: Dr. Van, 12/22/1955 (Box 1168, Folder 7)
      On item, "Dr. Van / Prod. #5523 / Music cue sheets sent: 12-22-55."
    - Episode 15: Of Caution and Courage, 12/22/1955 (Box 1168, Folder 8)
      On item, "Of Caution & Courage / Prod. #5522 / Cue sheets sent: 12-22-55."
    - Episode 25: Ninety Day Wonder, 02/08/1956 (Box 1168, Folder 9)